<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://amirmerfan.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://amirmerfan.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2026-01-30T13:25:40+00:00</updated><id>https://amirmerfan.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Amirmohammad Erfan</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Started MSc at Bilkent University</title><link href="https://amirmerfan.github.io/blog/2026/master-bilkent-begin/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Started MSc at Bilkent University"/><published>2026-01-22T09:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2026-01-22T09:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://amirmerfan.github.io/blog/2026/master-bilkent-begin</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://amirmerfan.github.io/blog/2026/master-bilkent-begin/"><![CDATA[<p>I am delighted to announce that today marks the official start of my graduate studies. I have joined the <strong>Department of Computer Engineering at Bilkent University</strong> as a Master’s student.</p> <p>I am privileged to be conducting my research under the supervision of <strong><a href="https://www.cs.bilkent.edu.tr/~cicek/">Prof. Ercument Cicek</a></strong>. Our work will focus on <strong>Genomic Privacy</strong>—addressing the critical security challenges inherent in processing and sharing sensitive biological data.</p> <p>Transitioning from my undergraduate studies at METU to this new role at Bilkent represents a significant step in my academic career. I look forward to contributing to the lab’s research and tackling complex problems at the intersection of bioinformatics and privacy-preserving technologies.</p> <blockquote> <p>“Privacy is not an option, and it shouldn’t be the price we accept for just getting on the internet.” — Gary Kovacs</p> </blockquote> <p>I am excited for the journey ahead!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="news"/><category term="masters"/><category term="bilkent"/><category term="research"/><category term="career"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Officially joining the Department of Computer Engineering under Prof. Ercument Cicek.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Award-Winning Paper Presented at NLPCL 2025</title><link href="https://amirmerfan.github.io/blog/2025/rag-nlpcl-paper-copy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Award-Winning Paper Presented at NLPCL 2025"/><published>2025-09-27T16:40:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-09-27T16:40:00+00:00</updated><id>https://amirmerfan.github.io/blog/2025/rag-nlpcl-paper%20copy</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://amirmerfan.github.io/blog/2025/rag-nlpcl-paper-copy/"><![CDATA[<p>I am proud to announce that our research paper, <strong>“From Voice to Code: A RAG-Enhanced Pipeline for Robust Multi-Accent Order Processing,”</strong> was successfully presented today at the <strong>6th International Conference on Natural Language Processing and Computational Linguistics (NLPCL 2025)</strong>.</p> <p>This work, which originated from my undergraduate research at <strong>Middle East Technical University (METU)</strong>, was honored with the <strong>Most Effective Research Award</strong> earlier this year.</p> <h3 id="project-overview">Project Overview</h3> <p>The paper introduces a pipeline that combines Automatic Speech Recognition (ASR) with Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) to handle diverse accents in technical command environments. By providing context to the model before it generates code (JSON), we significantly reduced error rates compared to standard transcription methods.</p> <h3 id="watch-the-presentation">Watch the Presentation</h3> <p>You can watch the full conference presentation below, delivered by me and my co-author, <strong>Taha Khan</strong>.</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <iframe width="100%" height="400" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/9DZtAM2Ocdg" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen=""></iframe> </div> </div> <h3 id="publication-status">Publication Status</h3> <p>We received our acceptance notification in <strong>August 2025</strong>, and the paper is now available via the Computer Science &amp; Information Technology Conference Proceedings (CSITCP).</p> <ul> <li><strong>Read the Paper:</strong> <a href="https://csitcp.org/abstract/15/1518csit04.php">Available on CSITCP</a></li> <li><strong>Conference:</strong> NLPCL 2025</li> <li><strong>Status:</strong> Published &amp; Presented (Sept 27, 2025)</li> </ul> <hr/> <blockquote> <p>“We aim to bridge the gap between the advancement in ASR and the persistent real-world challenges that still hinder accuracy.”</p> </blockquote> <p>This project marks a significant milestone in my academic journey as I transition into my Master’s studies at Bilkent University.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="news"/><category term="research"/><category term="nlp"/><category term="award"/><category term="presentation"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Presentation of "From Voice to Code" at NLPCL 2025. Co-authored with Taha Khan.]]></summary></entry></feed>